After finding out details about a stranger, we mistakenly think that they also know about us.
了解到一个陌生人的详细情况后，我们会误以为对方也了解我们。
As a result, we act more honestly around them, according to a recent study in Nature.
《自然》杂志最近的一项研究表明，正因如此，我们在对方面前会表现得更诚实。
Past research has found that we tend to assume social relationships are reciprocal.
以往的研究发现，我们往往会认为社会关系是相互的。
Most of the time, this assumption is accurate: someone you think of as a friend will usually consider you a friend too.
大多数时候，这种看法是准确的：你视为朋友的人，通常也会把你当作朋友。
But sometimes our social ties are more one-sided: for example, you might learn something about a stranger who doesn’t know you at all.
但有时，我们的社会联系更多是单方面的：比如，你可能了解到某个陌生人的一些情况，而对方根本不认识你。
Researchers Anuj Shah and Michael LaForest wondered whether our tendency to believe that social ties are reciprocal could lead us to mistakenly feel that a stranger does actually know us.
研究人员阿努杰·沙阿和迈克尔·拉福雷斯特想知道，我们倾向于认为社会联系是相互的，这种倾向是否会让我们误以为某个陌生人真的了解我们。
In a series of lab-based studies, this is exactly what the researchers found.
在一系列实验室研究中，研究人员发现的正是这种情况。
When we know about strangers, we erroneously think they also know about us.
我们一旦对陌生人有所了解，就会错误地以为对方也了解我们。
But the really interesting finding came when the researchers stepped out of the lab, to conduct a field experiment.
但真正有意思的发现，出现在研究人员走出实验室、开展实地实验的时候。
The team developed leaflets containing fairly ordinary information about local community police officers, such as their favourite food, hobbies, or reasons for joining the police force.
研究团队制作了传单，上面印着当地社区警察相当普通的一些信息，比如他们最喜欢的食物、爱好或加入警队的原因。
They then sent out these leaflets to every apartment in a number of housing developments in disadvantaged areas.
随后，他们把这些传单送到贫困地区若干住宅小区的每一户。
The officers themselves also dropped off cards containing similar information for local residents.
警察本人也给当地居民送去了载有类似信息的卡片。
Two months later, the researchers surveyed residents at these housing developments as well as control areas that did not receive leaflets or outreach cards.
两个月后，研究人员调查了这些住宅小区的居民，也调查了对照地区的居民——这些地区既没收到传单，也没收到外联卡片。
Residents were asked to imagine that they had committed a crime and to say how likely it would be that local officers would find out about it.
研究人员请居民想象自己犯了罪，并说出当地警察查出此事的可能性有多大。
They also rated how well the officers in the area knew them.
居民们还评估了该地区的警察对自己有多了解。
The team found that residents of the developments that had received the leaflets believed it more likely that local officers would find out about illegal activity than residents of the control areas.
研究团队发现，与对照地区的居民相比，收到过传单的住宅小区居民认为当地警察发现违法活动的可能性更大。
Even more strikingly, the team found that immediately after the leaflet distribution, there were fewer criminal complaints and arrests in the areas around the developments that had received the leaflets than around the control developments.
更引人注目的是，研究团队发现，传单刚一发放，收到传单的住宅小区周边的刑事投诉和逮捕数量就都比对照小区周边少。